<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backup and Restore on The Official Site of siBunglon</title>
    <link>https://sibunglon.com/tags/backup-and-restore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backup and Restore on The Official Site of siBunglon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 14:26:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
      <atom:link href="https://sibunglon.com/tags/backup-and-restore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Backup and Restore Database SQL Server to Lower Version</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2019/05/16/backup-and-restore-database-sql-server-to-lower-version/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 14:26:00 +0700</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2019/05/16/backup-and-restore-database-sql-server-to-lower-version/</guid>
        <description>How to Restore Database SQL server to lower version?
If you want to migrate a database from environment A with SQL Server version A to environment B with SQL Server version A, you can use the script or backup and restore function. But if you want to migrate the database from environment A with SQL Server version A to environment B with SQL Server version B, when running the backup function in environment A and you will get problems when running the restore function in environment B.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Backup VM Proxmox ke Local HardDisk</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2017/10/19/backup-vm-proxmox-ke-local-harddisk/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2017/10/19/backup-vm-proxmox-ke-local-harddisk/</guid>
        <description>A. PendahuluanPada kesempatan ini saya share bagaimana agar config di debian atau apapun yang ada diproxmox tidak hilang bila terjadi sesuatuB. PengertianBakcup data adalah salah satu langkah untuk menyimpan data agar saat data itu hilang kita masih memiliki data simpanannya agar tidak hilang.C. Latar belakangMembuat secondary data agar saat data primer nya hilang kita masih punya data secondari nya.D. TujuanAgar data yang saat penting itu tidak hilang karena ada kesalahan dan dapat menyerlamatkan pekerjaan kita.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Backup and Restore Mikrotik</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2017/09/22/backup-and-restore-mikrotik/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 03:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2017/09/22/backup-and-restore-mikrotik/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Recovery Data Dari Hardisk atau Flashdisk Yang Tidak Bisa Dibuka</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2017/08/22/recovery-data-dari-hardisk-atau-flashdisk-yang-tidak-bisa-dibuka/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2017/08/22/recovery-data-dari-hardisk-atau-flashdisk-yang-tidak-bisa-dibuka/</guid>
        <description></description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
