<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Case Study on The Official Site of siBunglon</title>
    <link>https://sibunglon.com/tags/case-study/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Case Study on The Official Site of siBunglon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 15:59:55 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
      <atom:link href="https://sibunglon.com/tags/case-study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Failed to Install the Following Android SDK Packages as Some Licences Have Not Been Accepted</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2019/05/19/failed-to-install-the-following-android-sdk-packages-as-some-licences-have-not-been-accepted/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 15:59:55 +0700</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2019/05/19/failed-to-install-the-following-android-sdk-packages-as-some-licences-have-not-been-accepted/</guid>
        <description>A few days ago, I had time to try to build an Android project but did not use the Android Studio application but instead used the command line. In order for the source code to be built using only the command line, we can use the included sdkmanager to download other SDK packages, this is a basic Android command line tool, if you want to download visit the Android Developer page then adjust with your environment.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Diam Diam Port 443 Lagi Konflik</title>
        <link>https://sibunglon.com/2019/03/26/diam-diam-port-443-lagi-konflik/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 14:26:11 +0700</pubDate>
        <guid>https://sibunglon.com/2019/03/26/diam-diam-port-443-lagi-konflik/</guid>
        <description>Beberapa hari yang lalu lagi ada ide iseng nyobain main-main vm linux (virtual machine) menggunakan VMware Workstation Pro, niatnya mau online-nin semua vm yang telah dibuat tapi cuman punya 1 ip publik. Emang bisa? Terus gimana ngaksesnya/ngeremotenya? Bisa dong, waktu itu pake port forwarding untuk NAT di VMware Workstation Pro, karena maunya si vm tersebut dapat akses internet dan dapat diakses dari 1 ip public.
Saya butuh web service yang dapat diakses melalui 1 publik yaitu 1 ip publik hostnya, okey saya pasang web service di salah satu vm.</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
